Guide to the Richard and Mildred Crooks Collection
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound
- Sound recordings
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC NetDec. 20, 1943, Transcription disc: ? rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    Part V (other parts missing)
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Net1943, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. Mother Mc Cree.
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Net1943, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. America the beautiful -- The hills of home
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Net1943, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. When you're away
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Net1943, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. The last hour
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Net1943, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. Reve -- Neapolitan love song
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Net1943, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. Passing by
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Net1943, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. Eternal father -- Somewhere a voice is calling
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Net1943, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. Oh Lord, most holy -- My message
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Net1943, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. For you alone -- Ah, moon of my delight
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC NetSept. 11, 1944, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. Parts 1 and 2 of 4
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC NetSept. 11, 1944, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. Parts 3 and 4 of 4
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC NetOct. 2, 1944, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC NetOct. 2, 1944, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC NetNov.15, 1944, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 18)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. Parts 1 and 2 of 2
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC NetJan. 19, 1945, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. Parts1 and 2 of 6
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC NetJan. 19, 1945, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 20)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. Parts 3 and 4 of 6
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC NetJan. 19, 1945, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    Howard Barlow and the Firestone Orchestra. Parts 5 and 6 of 6
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC NetFeb. 17, 1945, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC NetFeb. 17, 1945, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC NetOct. 24, 1978, Test pressing disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC NetOct. 24, 1978, Test pressing disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Netundated, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 26)
    Side 1: Homing -- Song of the Volga boatman -- Do not go my love -- If thou be near -- going home.Side 2: The bell man -- Lindy you -- The Lord's prayer
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Netundated, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 27)
    Side 1: Thine alone -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Largo -- Pourquoi me réveiller -- Take a pair of sparkling eyesSide 2: My wild Irish rose -- Dawn of freedom
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Netundated, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 28)
    Side 1: None but the lonely heart -- Where e'er you walkSide 2: Come love with me -- Home on the range
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Netundated, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 29)
    Side 1: Retreat -- Chevauchee cosaque -- Last hour -- My messageSide 2: Church's one foundation -- Hills of home -- May night
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Netundated, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 30)
    Drink to me only with thine eyes -- At Christmas time
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Netundated, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 31)
    Side 1: Dedication -- Waltzing Matilda -- To the children -- Jesu joy of man's desiringSide 2: Trek song -- Donkey serenade -- Prayer of thanksgiving -- Christmas candle
  - Voice of Firestone (Radio program): Richard Crooks. NBC Netundated, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 32)
    Hills of home
  - Voice of Firestone (?): Richard Crooks. undated, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 34)
    Over there -- Berceuse
  - Voice of Firestone (?): Richard Crooks. undated, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 35)
    Side 1: Marseillaise -- Army Air Corp. -- Marines HymnSide 2: Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Rom#233;o et Juliette. Farewell aria.
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda (in German)Berlin 1927, Test pressing: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 36)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda. Holde Aïda
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda (in German)Berlin 1927, Test pressing: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 37)
    Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda. Holde Aïda (duplicate?)
  - Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Salut, demeure chaste et pure Oct. 6, 1937, Test pressing: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Lalo, Edouard, 1823-1892. Roi d'Ys. Aubade. Vainement, ma bien-aim#233;e Oct. 8, 1937, Test pressing: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. Ah! fuyez, douce image. (Act 3)Apr. 22, 1938, Test pressing: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Pêcheurs de perles. Je crois entendre encore. (Act 1) Feb. 16, 1939, Test pressing: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Cil#232;a, Francesco, 1866-1950. Arlesiana. #200; la solita storia Feb. 16, 1939, Test pressing: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Part 1 and 21939, Transcription disc: ? rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 43)
    Performers: Jepson, Helen, 1904-; Crooks, Richard, 1900-1972; Tibbett, Lawrence, 1896-1960.
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Part 3 and 41939, Transcription disc: ? rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Part 5 and 61939, Transcription disc: ? rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Act I, scene 1 and 2Apr. 6, 1940, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 46)
    Performers: Jepson, Helen, 1904-; Olheim, Helen; Votikpa, Thelma; Crooks, Richard, 1900-1972; Warren, Leonard, 1911-1960; Pinza, Ezio. Chorus and orchestra of the Metropolitan Opera Company. Pelletier, Wilfrid, 1896-1982, conductor.Pelletier, Wilfrid, 1896-1982
  - Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Act I, scene 1 and 2 (duplicate)Apr. 6, 1940, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Act IIApr. 6, 1940, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Act II (duplicate)Apr. 6, 1940, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Act IIIApr. 6, 1940, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Act III (duplicate)Apr. 6, 1940, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Partenope. Sei mia giojaSept. 16, 1940, Transcription disc: ? rpm, acetate; 10 in. (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Partenope. Sei mia gioja (duplicate)Sept. 16, 1940, Transcription disc: ? rpm, acetate; 10 in. (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Floridante. Alma mia Sept. 16, 1940, Transcription disc: ? rpm, acetate; 10 in. (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Lohengrin (selection)Nov. 11, 1948, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, plastic; 12 in. (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - The Golden Age of Opera. Potpurri (5)1936-1948, LP disc: 33 1/3 rpm, plastic; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 56)
    Side 1: Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Samson et Dalila. J'ai gravi la montagne -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. De' miei bollenti spiriti -- Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Lucia di Lammermoor. Selections. Cruda, funesta smania -- Pallor funesto -- Dalle stanze ove Lucia.Side 2: Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Otello. Ora e per sempre addio -- Mascagni, Pietro, 1863-1945. Cavalleria rusticana. Voi lo sapete -- Strauss, Richard, 1864-1949. Salome. Finale -- Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Musensohn -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Walküre. Ho-jo-to-ho!
  - The Golden Age of Opera. Potpurri (6)1936-1948, LP disc: 33 1/3 rpm, plastic; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 57)
    Side 1: Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Tosca. E lucevan le stelle; Recondita armonia -- Traubel and Carron. Man without a country: My dearest: My own; My life -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Walküre. Ho-jo-to-ho! -- Smetana, Bedrich, 1824-1884. Prodan#225; nevesta. Selection -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Libiamo ne lieti calici -- Hahn, Reynaldo, 1875-1947. Ciboulette. Ce n'#233;tait pas la même chose.Side 2: Pergolesi, Giovanni Battista, 1710-1736. Tre giorni son che Nina -- De Curtis, Ernesto, 1875-1937. Torna a Surriento -- Bellini, Vincenzo, 1801-1835. Norma. Casta diva -- Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Fille du r#233;giment. Selection -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Don Giovanni. Selection -- Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci. Vesti la giubba -- Thomas, Ambroise, 1811-1896. Mignon. Selection -- Flotow, Friedrich von, 1812-1883. Martha. Selection -- Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Zauberflöte. O Isis und Osiris (Aria); In diesen heil'gen Hallen
  - The Golden Age of Opera. Richard Crooks, tenor1938-1943, LP disc: 33 1/3 rpm, plastic; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 58)
    Side 1: Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Werther. Pourquoi me r#233;veiller -- Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Serse. Ombra mai f#249; -- Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, 1844-1908. Sadko. A song of India -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Lohengrin. Mein lieber Schwan -- Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Elisir d'amore. Furtiva lagrima -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Walküre. Winterstürme wichen dem Wonnemond -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Un d#xEC felice, eterea; De' miei bollenti spiriti Side 2: Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Traviata. Questa donna; Parigi, o cara, noi lasceremo -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. A moi les plaisirs; Salut, demeure chaste et pure -- Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. En fermant les yeux je vois; Ah! fuyez, douce image
  - The Golden Age of Opera. Richard Crooks, tenor (duplicate)1938-1943, LP disc: 33 1/3 rpm, plastic; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Fleur que tu m'avais jet#233;e, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Fleur que tu m'avais jet#233;e (duplicate?), Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Rimsky-Korsakov, Nikolay, 1844-1908. Sadko. A song of India, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Elisir d'amore. Furtiva lagrima, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Elisir d'amore. Furtiva lagrima (duplicate?), Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Rigoletto. Donna #232; mobile, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Rigoletto. Donna #232; mobile (duplicate?), Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Song of Bayou and Two American sketchesDec. 28, 1928, Custom pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - My sunshine is youDec. 22, 1931, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - My wild Irish rose March, 1933, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - So we'll go no moreApr. 26, 1934, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - If I should send a roseJune 24, 1935, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - At the Mardi GrasFeb. 23, 1936, Test pressing disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - "The Singing Lady" presents "The Story of Richard Crooks" Parts 1 and 2 of 3Nov. 18, 1937, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - "The Singing Lady" presents "The Story of Richard Crooks" Part 3 of 3Nov. 18, 1937, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Fedora. Selection Feb.16, 1939, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Floridante. Alma mia Sept.16, 1940, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Have you seen but a whyte lilie grow?Sept.16, 1940, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Have you seen but a whyte lilie grow? (duplicate?)Sept.16, 1940, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Grieg, Edvard, 1843-1907. Lieder, op. 48. Traum Sept.16, 1940, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Quilter, Roger, 1877-1953. Songs, op. 3. Now sleeps the crimson petal Sept.16, 1940, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Pessard, Emile, 1843-1917. Adieu du matin Sept.18, 1940, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Pessard, Emile, 1843-1917. Adieu du matin (duplicate?)Sept.18, 1940, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Elegies, medium voice, violoncello, piano Jan. 16, 1942, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Judas Maccabaeus. Sound an alarm Jan. 16, 1942, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Handel, George Frideric, 1685-1759. Samson. Total eclipse Jan. 16, 1942, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847. Elias. So ihr mich von ganzem Herzen suchet June 8, 1942, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Mendelssohn-Bartholdy, Felix, 1809-1847. Elias. Dann werden die Gerechten June 8, 1942, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - War Department Music Branch. Popular songsMay 8, 1944, V disc: 78 rpm, plastic; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 88)
    My wild Irish rose -- Loch Lomond -- Turn ye to me
  - Balfe, M. W. (Michael William), 1808-1870. Killarney Nov.16, 1948, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, plastic; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - Ave Maria and Campton Races MedleyMar. 14, 1949, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - Ave Maria and Campton Races Medley (duplicate?)Mar. 14, 1949, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - BaroniMay 11, 1964, Instantaneous disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 92)
  - Prop 14, "No" COMMOct. 29, 1964, Instantaneous disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - Florists' Telegraph Delivery. California Spot Campaign. "Personal Gift"Dec. 25, 1964, Instantaneous disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 94)
  - Music from Elayne Girffith's WeddingApr. 8, 1967, Instantaneous disc: 33 1/3 rpm, plastic; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - Music from Elayne Girffith's Wedding (duplicate)Apr. 8, 1967, Instantaneous disc: 33 1/3 rpm, plastic; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 96)
  - Wedding of Mr. & Mrs. Thomas A. TechentinApr. 8, 1967, Instantaneous disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 15, Folder 97)
    Wilshire Methodist Church. Includes a disc cover with dedication to Richard and Mildred Crooks
  - Americans Come Parts 1 and 2 of 3Dec. 12, 19?, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 98)
  - Americans Come Part 3 of 3Dec. 12, 19?, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 99)
  - A San Francisco Original Gold Seal. "The Ballad of Governor Mac Heath.", souvenir disc: 45 rpm, plastic; 6 3/4 in. (Box 15, Folder 100)
    Ron the Knife arranged and sung by Earl' Fatha Hines
  - Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Tosca (selection) and Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Fedora (selection), Transcription disc: ? rpm, acetate; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 101)
  - "At Christmastime" and "Christmas Candle", Custom pressing disc: 78 rpm, plastic; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 102)
  - Chenoweth, Wilbur, 1899-1980. Variations on "Lobe den Herren", Custom pressing disc: 78 rpm, plastic; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 103)
    Los Angeles Philharmonic. Wallenstein, Alfred, conductor.
  - Templeton, Alec, 1910-1963. Gifts, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 104)
    Bonelli, Mona, lyrics. Bonelli Richard, piano
  - Springtime reminds me of you, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 105)
  - I love thee, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 106)
  - Prayer Perfect, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 107)
  - My song goes 'round the world, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 108)
  - O song divine, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 109)
  - Waltz song, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (Box 15, Folder 110)
  - How lovely are thy dwellings, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 111)
  - Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Schöne Müllerin (selections), Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 112)
    Wandern -- Wohin -- Halt
  - Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Schöne Müllerin (selections), Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 113)
    Danksagung an dem Bach; Am Feierabend
  - Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Schöne Müllerin (selections), Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 114)
    Mit dem grünen Lautenbande -- Jäger -- Eifersucht und Stolz
  - Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Schöne Müllerin (selections), Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (disc cracked) (Box 16, Folder 115)
    Die liebe Farbe; Die böse Farbe
  - Thora, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 116)
  - Nirvana, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 117)
  - Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Pêcheurs de perles. Je crois entendre encore, V disc: 78 rpm, plastic; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 118)
  - Richard Crooks, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 119)
  - Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Ellens Gesang, D. 839 and Burleigh, (Harry Thacker), 1866-1949. Were you there, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 120)
  - Oratorio arias (test recording), Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 121)
  - Thru my open window and Christmas Candle, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 122)
  - Concert, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 123)
  - When you're away and Ay-Ay-Ay, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 124)
  - Over there, Transcription disc: 33 1/3 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 125)
  - Sailing Homeward, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 126)
  - Songs my mother taught me, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 127)
  - Songs my mother taught me (duplicate), Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 128)
  - Songs my mother taught me (duplicate), Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 129)
  - Songs my mother taught me (duplicate), Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 130)
  - Mail call, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 131)
  - Mail call (duplicate), Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 132)
  - Land of hope and glory, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 133)
  - Lullaby from Joselyn, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 10 in. (Box 16, Folder 134)
  - Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Rom#233;o et Juliette (selection) and I love thee, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 135)
  - Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Rom#233;o et Juliette (selection) and I love thee (duplicate?), Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 136)
  - Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Rom#233;o et Juliette (selection); I love thee and Drink to me only with thine eyes, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 137)
  - Bach, Johann Sebastian, 1685-1750. Matthäuspassion (abridged), Custom pressing disc: 33 1/3 rpm, plastic; 12 in. (Box 16, Folder 138)
  - Mail Call, Transcription disc: 78 rpm, acetate; 12 in. (disc cracked) (Box 17, Folder 139)
  - Ave MariaJune 8, 1942, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (disc broken) (Box 16, Folder 140)
  - Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Schöne Müllerin. Trockene Blumen, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (disc cracked) (Box 16, Folder 141)
  - Schubert, Franz, 1797-1828. Schöne Müllerin. Der Müller und der Bach, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 12 in. (disc broken) (Box 6, Folder 142)
  - Arne, Thomas Augustine, 1710-1778. Comus (selection) and Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Lieder, 2. T. O liebes Mädchen, höre mich, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (disc cracked) (Box 16, Folder 143)
  - Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Werther. Pourquoi me r#233;veiller, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (disc broken and cracked) (Box 16, Folder 144)
  - Too late tomorrow, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (disc cracked) (Box 16, Folder 145)
  - Until, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (disc broken) (Box 16, Folder 146)
  - Springtime reminds me of you, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (disc cracked) (Box 16, Folder 147)
  - Vienna, city of dreams, Test pressing disc: 78 rpm, shellac; 10 in. (disc broken) (Box 16, Folder 148)